http://www.chemistshop.co.nz/pages/privacy-policy

Newsletter
Subscribe to our newsletter to get our latest news, deals and promotions right into your inbox.
Antihistamine Nasal & SinusEye DropsDigestive Care
HaemorrhoidIndigestion & HeartburnDehydrationWormsDiarrhoeaConstipationNasal & Sinus CareSkincare
Eczema & DermatitisAnti-FungalsScabiesWound careBites and RashesAnti-InflammatoriesAcneDry & Sensitive SkinWashes & SoapsDeodorantScar & Stretch Mark Oral Care
Mouth UlcerCold soresSore ThroatLip BalmTravel Medicine
Travel SicknessDiarrhoeaBites and RashesSports & First Aid
First AidSportDressing, Tape & Support
DressingTapeSupportPlastersHands & Foot Care
Wart & Corn RemovalAnti-FungalsFungal Nail InfectionCracked Hands & FeetNail PolishInner Sole & AccessoriesHair & Scalp Care
DandruffHead LiceShampoo & ConditionerEczema & DermatitisEye Care
Dry EyeAllergyConjunctivitisStyeEar CareWomen Health
Vaginal ThrushUrinary Tract InfectionsFeminine HygienePregnancySexual HealthPPE
Face MaskSanitiserMother & Baby
Baby & ChildPregnancyMomDiagnostic Products
Glucose MeterBlood Pressure MonitorPregnancy TestDrug TestNatural Health & Supplement
VitaminsMineralsNatural HealthSpecialised NutritionNZ MADE
Manuka HoneyContact
1.          Your privacy
Our privacy policy is strong and precise. It complies fully with current law.
By using the Our Website, you give us authorisation to collect your personal information and we provide you with the right to:
see, and if necessary correct, the information
restrict or delete your information
be informed who can access to your information and how your information is being used
complain to appropriate authority
We can ensure that we will not sell your information. We use your information to:
fulfil your order
ensure that the medicines and products that are supplied to you by us are appropriate for you.
improve our business
when the information is required by law to be provided.
We only disclose your information to third parties only to the extent to run our business, to our service providers, to fulfil any orders from you.
We use Shopify to host our Website --you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy
We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site -- you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
We may update our privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
If you have any concerns regarding your privacy, please let us know by sending us e-mail to info@chemistshop.co.nz or info@wirihealthpharmacy.com.
If you Post Content to any public area of Our Website it becomes available in the public domain. We have no control who sees it or what anyone does with it.
Even if access to your text is behind a user registration it remains effectively in the public domain because someone has only to register and log in, to access it. You should therefore avoid Posting unnecessary confidential information.
You understand that you are personally responsible for your breach of someone else’s intellectual property rights, defamation, or any law, which may occur as a result of any Content having been Posted by you.
Please notify us of any security breach or unauthorised use of your account.
We do not solicit ideas or text for improvement of our Service, but if you do send to us material of any sort, you are deemed to have granted us a licence to use it.
Subscribe to our newsletter
to get our latest news, deals and promotions right into your inbox.
100% free, Unsubscribe any time!
FREE New Zealand Shipping For Order Over $99
Secure payments
14 Days Returns Policy
Top-notch Customer Support
